Granville Hicks Papers
Granville Hicks Papers
- Correspondence - subject files
  - Chicago Tribune (Box 12)
  - Chilmark Press (Box 13)
  - Chilton Company (Box 13)
  - Chopin, Kate (Box 13)
  - The Christian Century (Box 13)
  - Christian, Henry A. (Box 13)
  - Christesen, Clement Byrne (Box 13)
  - Christman, Henry, 1937-1951; 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Christowe, Stroyan (Box 13)
  - Citron, Minna (Wright) (Box 13)
  - Claire, William F. (Box 13)
  - Clancy, Judith S. (Box 13)
  - Claremont Journal of Political Economy (Box 13)
  - Clark, C.E. Frazer (Box 13)
  - Clark, E. Everett (Box 13)
  - Clark, Eleanor (Box 13)
  - Clark, Thomas Blake (Box 13)
  - Clarke, Edwin Leavitt (Box 13)
  - Clarkson, Gary (Box 13)
  - Cleghorn, Sarah Norcliffe (Box 13)
  - Clemens, Cyril (Box 13)
  - Clemens, Samuel Langhorne, See Twain, Mark.
  - Clements, Albert (Box 13)
  - Coates, Robert M. (Box 13)
    See also Yaddo.
  - Coggeshall, Reginald (Box 13)
  - Cohen, Elliot E. (Box 13)
  - Cohen, Morris Raphael (Box 13)
  - Colby Junior College (Box 13)
  - Cole, George, 1941-1960; undated; 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Cole, Lois Dwight (Box 13)
    See also Putnam's, G.P.; Macmillan Company.
  - Coleman, Richard (Box 13)
  - Coleridge, Samuel Taylor (Box 13)
  - College Center of the Finger Lakes (Box 13)
  - Collier, Franklin P. (Box 13)
  - Collier, P.F. and Son Corporation (Box 13)
  - Collins, John H. (Box 13)
  - Collins, Seward Bishop, See The Bookman.
  - Colorado Literary Festival (Box 13)
  - The Colorado Review (Box 13)
  - Colum, Mary M. (Box 13)
  - Columbia University Forum (Box 13)
  - Columbia University Press (Box 13)
  - Commager, Henry Steele (Box 13)
  - Commentary (Box 13)
  - Commins, Saxe (Box 13)
  - Committee on Mobilization (Box 13)
  - Committee to Aid Victims of German Fascism (Troy, NY) (Box 13)
  - Common Council for American Unity (Box 13)
  - Common Sense (Box 13)
  - Commonwealth College (Box 13)
  - Community life (Box 13)
  - Community Service, Inc. (Box 14)
  - Congress pour la Liberte de la Culture (Box 14)
  - Congressional Record - House, 1951; "How the Magazine The Nation is Serving Communism." (Box 14)
  - Conkling, Grace Hazard (Box 14)
  - Connery, Donald S. (Box 14)
  - Connecticut, University of (Box 14)
  - Conover, Harry (Box 14)
  - Conrad, Earl (Box 14)
  - Conrad, Joseph (Box 14)
  - Conroy, Jack (Box 14)
  - Contemporary Novelists of the English Language (Box 14)
  - Cook, Reginald Lansing (Box 14)
  - Cooke, Alistair (Box 14)
  - Cooke, Rose Terry (Box 14)
  - Coombs, Nellie (Box 14)
  - Coon, Horace (Box 14)
  - Cooper, James Fenimore (Box 14)
  - Cooper, Jane (Box 14)
  - Cooper, Lyle Winston (Box 14)
  - Cooper Union for the Advancement of Science and Art (Box 14)
  - Copeland, Charles Townsend (Box 14)
  - Corey, Lewis (Box 14)
  - Corey, Paul (Box 14)
  - Corman, Cid (Box 14)
  - Cornell University (Box 14)
  - Corrington, John William (Box 14)
  - Costa, Richard Hauer (Box 14)
  - Counts, George S. (Box 14)
  - Cousins, Norman (Box 14)
  - Coward-McCann, Inc. (Box 14)
  - Cowley, Malcolm, 1930-1973; undated; 7 folders (Box 14)
  - Cox, Sidney (Box 15)
  - Cozzens, James Gould, 3 folders (Box 15)
  - Craddock, Charles Egbert (Box 15)
  - Craig, George Armour (Box 15)
  - Crane, Hart (Box 15)
  - Crane, Stephen (Box 15)
  - Crawford, Francis Marion. An American Politician (Box 15)
  - Crichton, Kyle (Box 15)
  - Criterion Books (Box 15)
  - Critics Group (Box 15)
  - Critique (Box 15)
  - Croly, Herbert David (Box 15)
  - Cronyn, George (Box 15)
  - Thomas Y. Crowell Company (Box 15)
  - Cruden, Robert (Box 15)
  - Culmsee, Carlton Fordis (Box 15)
  - Cummins, Walter M. (Box 15)
  - Cunard, Nancy (Box 15)
  - Cunningham, Charles E. (Box 15)
  - Cunningham, William (Box 15)
  - Curley, Daniel (Box 15)
  - Curran Debate, 1939 (Box 15)
  - Curran, Edward Lodge, See Curran Debate.
  - Curti, Merle, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Curtis, Jack (Box 15)
  - Curto, Josephine J. (Box 15)
  - Cushing, Kenneth (Box 15)
  - Cuthbert, Clifton (Box 15)
  - D (Box 15)
  - Daedalus (Box 15)
  - Dahir, James (Box 15)
  - Dahlberg, Edward (Box 16)
  - Dakin, Wilson Sheldon (Box 16)
  - Daley, Robert (Box 16)
  - Dam, Hari N. (Box 16)
  - Damrosch, Frank (Box 16)
  - Dana, Henry Wadsworth Longfellow (Box 16)
  - Dana, Roger W. (Box 16)
  - Darcy, Sam Adams (Box 16)
  - Davenport, Russell Wheeler (Box 16)
  - Davis, Horace Bancroft (Box 16)
  - Davis, Jerome (Box 16)
  - Davis, Preston (Box 16)
  - Davis, Robert Gorham, 1931-1972; undated; 10 folders (Box 16)
  - Davis, Robert Gorham to Dorothy Hicks, 1931-1935; undated; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Davis, Stuart (Box 16)
  - Davis, Wallace. M. (Box 16)
  - Davison, Richard Allan (Box 16)
  - Dawkins, Cecil (Box 16)
  - John Day Company, Inc. (Box 16)
  - Deal, Borden (Box 16)
  - Decadence (Literary Movement) (Box 16)
  - DeFanti, Charles L. (Box 16)
  - DeJong, David Cornel (Box 16)
  - De Lima, Agnes (Box 16)
  - Dell, Floyd (Box 16)
  - DeMaria, Robert (Box 16)
  - Demos, Raphael (Box 16)
  - DeMott, Benjamin (Box 16)
  - Dempster, Milen (Box 16)
  - Denison University (Box 17)
  - Dennison, Henry Sturgis (Box 17)
  - Dennison job, 1923; 2 folders (Box 17)
  - De Toledano, Ralph (Box 17)
  - Deutsch, Albert (Box 17)
  - De Voto, Bernard (Box 17)
  - De Vries, Peter (Box 17)
  - John Dewey Society of Columbia University (Box 17)
  - Dial Press (Box 17)
  - Dialogue '68 (Box 17)
  - Dickens, Charles (Box 17)
  - Dictionary of American Biography (Box 17)
  - Dictionary of Quotations (Box 17)
  - Dilliard, Irving (Box 17)
  - Dinamov, Sergei, See International Literature.
  - Dirlam, Joel (Box 17)
  - Dishman, Robert B. (Box 17)
  - Disraeli, Benjamin (Box 17)
  - Dissent (Box 17)
  - Divine, Arthur Durham, See Rame, David.
  - Doctorow, E.L. (Box 17)
  - Dodd, Mead & Company, Inc. (Box 17)
  - Dodge, Mabel, See Luhan, Mabel Dodge.
  - Dollard, John (Box 17)
  - Dommergues, Pierre (Box 17)
  - Doonping, Richard (Box 17)
  - Doran, Marion (Box 17)
  - Dos Passos, John, 3 folders (Box 17)
  - Dostoyevsky, Fyodor (Box 17)
  - Doten, Dana (Box 17)
  - Doubleday & Company (Box 17)
  - Doubleday, Doran and Co. (Box 17)
  - Doubleday, Page and Co. (Box 17)
  - Doughty, Frances (Box 17)
  - Doughty, Howard N., 1932-1949; undated; 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Douglas, Laura W. (Box 18)
  - Downes, Randolph C. (Box 18)
  - Doxey, William S. (Box 18)
  - Drake, Robert (Box 18)
  - Drama and dramatists (Box 18)
  - Draper, Theodore (Box 18)
  - Dreifuss, Kurt (Box 18)
  - Dreiser, Theodore (Box 18)
  - Driskell, Leon vol. (Box 18)
  - Duell, Sloan & Pearce, Inc. (Box 18)
  - Dugan, James (Box 18)
  - Duhl, Leonard J. (Box 18)
  - Dunn, Robert Williams (Box 18)
  - Dunne, William F. (Box 18)
  - Dupee, Frederick Wilcox (Box 18)
  - Durrell, Lawrence (Box 18)
  - E.P. Dutton & Company, Inc. (Box 18)
  - E (Box 18)
  - Earnest, Ernest Penney (Box 18)
  - East and West Association (Box 18)
  - Eastman, Max (Box 18)
  - Eaton, Charles Edward (Box 18)
  - Eaton, Geoffrey Dell (Box 18)
  - Eaton, Joseph W. (Box 18)
  - Eddy, Roger (Box 18)
  - Edman, Irwin (Box 18)
  - Edmonds, Walter D. (Box 18)
  - Education, 3 folders (Box 18)
  - Eggleston, Edward (Box 18)
  - Ehrlich, Leonard (Box 18)
  - Eidson, John Olio (Box 18)
  - Eight Ways of Looking at Christianity (Box 18)
  - Einaudi Editore (Box 18)
  - Eisen, Arnold M. (Box 18)
  - Elder, James Rex (Box 18)
  - Eliot, George (Box 18)
  - Eliot, Samuel Atkins (Box 19)
  - Eliot, Thomas Stearns (Box 19)
  - Elliott, George P. (Box 19)
  - Ellison, Ralph (Box 19)
  - Emancipator (Box 19)
  - Emerson, Ralph Waldo (Box 19)
  - Encounter (Box 19)
  - Encyclopedia Britannica (Box 19)
  - Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences (Box 19)
  - Endore, S. Guy (Box 19)
  - English Journal (Box 19)
  - Engstrand, Stuart David (Box 19)
  - Enzer, Hyman A. (Box 19)
  - Erdman, David vol. (Box 19)
  - Ervin, Charles W. (Box 19)
  - Esquire (Box 19)
  - Ethel, Garland (Box 19)
  - Eulau, Heinz (Box 19)
  - Evans, Dilys (Box 19)
  - Evans, Ernestine (Box 19)
  - M. Evans and Company, Inc. (Box 19)
  - F (Box 19)
  - Fabian socialism (Box 19)
  - Fadiman, Clifton P. (Box 19)
  - Falk, Signi Lenea (Box 19)
  - Famous Writers School, 3 folders (Box 19)
  - Fante, John (Box 19)
  - Farina, Richard (Box 19)
  - Farmers - Political activity, 3 folders (Box 19)
  - Farrar & Rinehart, Inc. (Box 19)
  - Farrar, Strauss and Company (Box 19)
  - Farrar, Strauss and Cudahy, Inc. (Box 19)
  - Farrar, Strauss and Giroux, Inc. (Box 19)
  - Farrell, James T., 1934-1968; 4 folders (Box 20)
  - Farson, Negley (Box 20)
  - Fast, Howard (Box 20)
  - Faulkner, William, 6 folders (Box 20)
  - Feigenbaum, Lawrence H. (Box 20)
  - Feikema, Feike, See Manfred, Frederick.
  - Fein, Isaac M. (Box 20)
  - Feinberg, Abraham L. (Box 20)
  - Felix, David (Box 20)
  - Fenton, Charles A. (Box 20)
  - Ferguson, Charles William (Box 20)
  - Ferrini, Vincent (Box 20)
  - Ficke, Arthur Davison (Box 20)
  - Field, Alice (Wintrow) (Box 20)
  - Field, Sara B. (Box 20)
  - Fiess, Edward (Box 20)
  - Filene, William (Box 20)
  - Fincher, Ernest Barksdale (Box 20)
  - Findlater, Richard (Box 20)
  - Fineman, Irving (Box 20)
  - Finley, John Huston (Box 20)
  - The First to Awaken (Box 20)
  - Fischer, John (Box 20)
  - Fischer, Louis. "Problems of Soviet Writers", March 6, 1932 (Box 20)
  - Fisher, Alfred Young (Box 20)
  - Fisher, Dorothy Canfield (Box 20)
  - Fisher, Vardis (Box 20)
  - Fishman, Solomon (Box 21)
  - Fitch, Clyde (Box 21)
  - Fitchburg Sentinel (Box 21)
  - Fitzgerald, F. Scott (Box 21)
  - Fitzgerald/Hemingway Annual (Box 21)
  - Flaherty, Duane (Box 21)
  - Flores, Angel (Box 21)
  - Flynn, Elizabeth Gurley (Box 21)
  - Foerster, Norman (Box 21)
  - Follett, Wilson. "Town Against Country" (Box 21)
  - Folsom, Franklin, See League of American Writers.
  - Forbes, Allan W. (Box 21)
  - Forbes, Stephen Hathaway (Box 21)
  - Ford, Ford Madox (Box 21)
  - Ford, Jesse Hill (Box 21)
  - Ford Foundation (Box 21)
  - Ford Hall Forum, Inc. (Box 21)
  - Foreign Policy Association (Box 21)
  - Forrester, Joel (Box 21)
  - Forster, E.M. (Box 21)
  - The Forum (Box 21)
  - Forum of Politics (Box 21)
  - Fowlie, Wallace (Box 21)
  - Fox, Daniel M. (Box 21)
  - Fox, Renee C. (Box 21)
  - Fraley, E.S. (Box 21)
  - Frame, Janet (Box 21)
  - Frank, Moses Zebi (Box 21)
  - Frank, Nelson (Box 21)
  - Frank, Waldo (Box 21)
  - Frankfeld, Philip (Box 21)
  - Frazier, David L. (Box 21)
  - Frede, Richard (Box 21)
  - Frederic, Harold (Box 21)
  - Frederick, John Towner (Box 21)
  - Free Press of Glencoe (Box 21)
  - Freedman, Louis Alexander (Box 21)
  - Freedman, Morris (Box 21)
  - Freeman, Joseph, 1932-1958; undated; 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Freeman, Joseph. Proletarian Literature in the United States, Introduction (Box 21)
  - Freeman, Mary Eleanor (Wilkins) (Box 21)
  - The Freeman (Box 21)
    See also The Freeman Nov. 3, 1920 - vol. 2, no. 34.
  - Freethinkers of America (Box 22)
  - Freitag, George H. (Box 22)
  - Fremont-Smith, Eliot (Box 22)
  - Friedman, Joseph (Box 22)
  - Friedman, Philip Allan (Box 22)
  - Fritchman, Stephen H. (Box 22)
  - Frohock, William Merrill (Box 22)
  - Frost, Robert (Box 22)
  - Fry, Varian and Eileen (Box 22)
  - Fryer, Donald S. (Box 22)
  - Fuller, Henry Blake (Box 22)
  - Fuller, Hoyt (Box 22)
  - Fuller, Margaret (Box 22)
  - Fuller, Raymond Tifft (Box 22)
  - Funaroff, Sol (Box 22)
  - Fund for the Republic (Box 22)
  - Funk, Charles Earle (Box 22)
  - Funk and Wagnalls Company (Box 22)
  - Furcolowe, Charles (Box 22)
  - Furst, John Brown. "Progressives and Psychoanalysis", 1945 (Box 22)
  - G (Box 22)
  - Gabriel, Gilbert W. (Box 22)
  - Gaddis, William (Box 22)
  - Gafford, Charlotte K. (Box 22)
  - Galsworthy, John (Box 22)
  - Galt, William Egleston (Box 22)
  - Gannett, Lewis (Box 22)
  - Gans, Herbert J. (Box 22)
  - Gardiner, Harold C. (Box 22)
  - Gardner, John (Box 22)
  - Gardner, Martin (Box 22)
  - Gardner, Virginia (Box 22)
  - Garland, Hamlin (Box 22)
  - Garnsey, Morris E. (Box 22)
  - Garrison, Jesse James (Box 22)
  - Garrison, Lloyd K. (Box 22)
  - Gaskell, Elizabeth Cleghorn Stevenson (Box 22)
  - Gass, William H. (Box 22)
  - Gastroenterology (Box 22)
  - Gates, Arnold F. (Box 22)
  - Gates, John (Box 22)
  - Gaus, John Merriman (Box 22)
  - Gavin, Catherine (Box 22)
  - Gehman, Richard (Box 22)
  - Gelb, Arthur (Box 23)
  - Gelb, Barbara (Box 23)
  - Genesis West (Box 23)
  - Genung, Ursula, See Walker, Ursula Genung.
  - George Arents Research Library, See Syracuse University Library.
  - Georgia Review (Box 23)
    See also Wade, John Donald.
  - Gerahty, Digby George, See Standish, Robert.
  - Gerber, Philip L. (Box 23)
  - Gerber, Toby (Box 23)
  - Gersh, Gabriel (Box 23)
  - Gertz, Elmer (Box 23)
  - Gessner, Robert (Box 23)
  - Gibson, Elizabeth (Box 23)
  - Gibson, James Jerome (Box 23)
  - Gibson, Roland (Box 23)
  - Gibson, William Merriam (Box 23)
  - Gideonse, Harry D. (Box 23)
  - Gilkes, Lillian Barnard (Box 23)
  - Gilroy, William E. (Box 23)
  - Ginn and Company (Box 23)
  - Gissing, George Robert (Box 23)
  - Glasgow, Ellen (Box 23)
  - Glass, Montague Marsden (Box 23)
  - Glassley, Ray Hoard (Box 23)
  - Glass, Sylvia (Box 23)
  - Glazer, Dorothy (Box 23)
  - Glazer, Nathan (Box 23)
  - Glick, Nathan (Box 23)
  - Glicksberg, Charles Irving (Box 23)
  - Glintenkamp, Henry J. (Box 23)
  - Godin, Murray (Box 23)
  - Goepp, Ada (Box 23)
  - Gold, Herbert, 1954-1972; undated; 3 folders (Box 23)
  - Gold, Michael (Box 23)
  - Goldhoff, Martha (Box 23)
  - Golding, William (Box 23)
  - Goldman, Emma (Box 23)
  - Goldman, Eric Frederick (Box 23)
  - Goldstein, Malcolm (Box 23)
  - Goldstein, Martin (Box 23)
    See also "Speaking of Books".
  - Gollancz, Victor (Box 23)
  - Goodman, Eckert, See Goodman, Jules Eckert.
  - Goodman, Jules Eckert (Box 23)
  - Goodykuntz, William (Box 23)
  - Gordon, Arthur Ernest (Box 23)
  - Gordon, Dudley Chadwick (Box 23)
  - Gordon, Mac (Box 23)
  - Gordon, Mark D. (Box 23)
  - Gorham, Charles (Box 23)
  - Goyen, William (Box 23)
  - Graebel, Richard Paul (Box 23)
  - Grafton, Samuel (Box 23)
  - Grafton, NY, education (Box 24)
  - Grafton, NY, elections (Box 24)
  - Grafton, NY, finance, public (Box 24)
  - Grafton, NY, historical documents (Box 24)
  - Grafton, NY, history; 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Grafton, NY, survey (Box 24)
  - Grafton, NY, zoning (Box 24)
  - Grafton Community League, Inc. (Box 24)
  - Grafton Free Library (Box 24)
  - Grafton Planning Board (Box 24)
  - Grafton Post (Box 24)
  - Graham, John Alexander (Box 24)
  - Graham, Richard (Box 24)
  - Graham, Robert Bontine Cunninghame (Box 24)
  - Granbery, John C. (Box 24)
  - Grant, Ozro Franklin (Box 24)
  - Grattan, Clinton Hartley (Box 24)
  - Grau, Shirley Ann (Box 24)
  - Graubard, Mark (Box 24)
  - Graves, Robert (Box 24)
  - Great Britain, Economic conditions, History notes (Box 24)
  - Great Britain, Economic conditions,19th century (Box 24)
  - The Great Ideas Today (Box 24)
  - The Great Tradition (Box 24)
  - The Great Tradition, See Quadrangle Books.
  - Grebanier, Bernard (Box 24)
  - Green, Gilbert (Box 24)
  - Green, Henry (Box 24)
  - Green, James Albert (Box 24)
  - Green Mountain College (Box 24)
  - Green Mountain Junior College, See Green Mountain College.
  - Greenberg, Robert A. (Box 24)
  - Greene, Graham (Box 24)
  - Greenleaf, Richard P. (Box 24)
  - Greenwood Press, Inc. (Box 24)
  - Greenwood Reprint Corp. (Box 24)
  - Gregory, Alexander (Box 24)
  - Gregory, Horace (Box 24)
  - Grever, Barbara Ann (Box 24)
  - Grobstein, Clifford (Box 24)
  - Gronowicz, Antoni (Box 24)
  - Gross, Gerald (Box 24)
  - Gross, John J. (Box 24)
  - Grossman Publishers (Box 25)
  - Groton School (Box 25)
  - Grove Press (Box 25)
  - Gruliow, Leo (Box 25)
  - Grumbach, Doris (Box 25)
  - Grundy, J. Owen (Box 25)
  - Grunwald, Henry Anatole (Box 25)
  - Guerard, Albert (Box 25)
  - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1925-1970; 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Gulick, Edward (Box 25)
  - Gullason, Thomas A. (Box 25)
  - Gustafson, Eric (Box 25)
  - Guttmann, Allen (Box 25)
  - H (Box 25)
  - Haber, Tom Burns (Box 25)
  - Haddad, Abdul (Box 25)
  - Haggin, B.H. (Box 25)
  - Hagler, Margaret (Box 25)
  - Halberstadt, Maria (Box 25)
  - Hale, Edward Everett (Box 25)
  - Hale, Robert Sever (Box 25)
  - Hall, James B. (Box 25)
  - Hall, Joan Joffe (Box 25)
  - Hallgren, Mauritz Alfred (Box 25)
  - Hallam, Atlantis (Box 25)
  - Hallowell, Robert (Box 25)
  - Halper, Albert (Box 25)
  - Ham, Tom (Box 25)
  - Hamlin, Will (Box 25)
  - Hammond, J. L. and Barbara (Box 25)
  - Hampshire County Progressive Club Forum (Box 25)
  - Hankins, Frank Hamilton (Box 25)
  - Hanley, James (Box 25)
  - Hannum, John A. (Box 25)
  - Hansen, Harry (Box 25)
  - Hansome, Marius (Box 25)
  - Hanson, Pauline (Polly), See Yaddo.
  - Hapgood, Hutchins (Box 25)
  - Harap, Henry (Box 25)
  - Harap, Louis (Box 25)
  - Harcourt, Brace and Company (Box 25)
  - Harcourt, Brace and World, Inc. (Box 25)
  - Hard, William (Box 25)
  - Hardwick, Elizabeth (Box 25)
  - Hardy, Thomas (Box 25)
  - Harington, Donald (Box 25)
  - Harland, Henry (Box 25)
  - Harlow, Ralph Volney (Box 25)
  - Harlow, Samuel Ralph (Box 25)
  - Harnack, Curtis (Box 26)
  - Harper, Martha Barnhart (Box 26)
  - Harper & Brothers (Box 26)
  - Harper & Row (Box 26)
  - Harper's Bazaar (Box 26)
  - Harper's Magazine (Box 26)
  - Harpur College (Box 26)
  - Harrington, Alan (Box 26)
  - Harrington House (Box 26)
  - Harris, Joel Chandler (Box 26)
  - Harris, Leon A. (Box 26)
  - Harris, Mark (Box 26)
  - Harris, Robert J. (Box 26)
  - Harrison, Gilbert A. (Box 26)
  - Harrison, Henry (Box 26)
  - Harrison, Joseph (Box 26)
  - Hart, Albert Bushnell (Box 26)
  - Hart, Alfred L. (Box 26)
  - Hart, Henry (Box 26)
  - Hart, James David (Box 26)
  - Hart, John Edward (Box 26)
  - Harte, Bret (Box 26)
  - Hartwick College (Box 26)
  - Harvard Communist (Box 26)
  - Harvard Crimson (Box 26)
  - Harvard Progressive (Box 26)
  - Harvard-Sacco-Vanzetti Committee (Box 26)
  - Harvard University (Box 26)
  - Harvard University, library (Box 26)
  - Harvard University, response to appointment (Box 26)
  - Harvard University Nieman Foundation for Journalism (Box 26)
  - Harvard University Press (Box 26)
  - Harvey, Lashley Grey (Box 26)
  - Haskell, Edward F. (Box 26)
  - Hassan, Ihab H. (Box 26)
  - Haste, Gwendolen (Box 26)
  - Hatfield, Walter Wilbur, See English Journal.
  - Hawkes, John (Box 26)
  - Hawkins, Maude Miller (Box 26)
  - Hawthorne, Hazel (Box 26)
  - Hawthorne, Nathaniel (Box 26)
  - Hay, John (Box 27)
  - Haycraft, Howard (Box 27)
  - Haydn, Hiram (Box 27)
  - Hayes, Alfred (Box 27)
  - Hayes, Charles Edward (Box 27)
  - Hays, Arthur Garfield (Box 27)
  - Hays, Robert Wilson (Box 27)
  - Hazlitt, Henry (Box 27)
  - Healey, Jim (Col.) (Box 27)
  - Healy, Arthur K.D. (Box 27)
  - Healy, John Vincent (Box 27)
  - Hearn, Lafcadio (Box 27)
  - D.C. Heath and Company (Box 27)
  - Heaton, John Langdon (Box 27)
  - Hedley, David (Box 27)
  - Heller, Joseph (Box 27)
  - Hemingway, Ernest, 3 folders (Box 27)
  - Henderson, Harry B. (Box 27)
  - Henley, William Ernest (Box 27)
  - Henry, O., See Porter, William Sydney.
  - Hepburn, James G. (Box 27)
  - Herald, Leon Srabian (Box 27)
  - Herbst, Josephine (Box 27)
  - Herdman, Ramona (Box 27)
  - Hergesheimer, Joseph (Box 27)
  - Herman, Hazel (Box 27)
  - Herrick, Robert (Box 27)
  - Hersey, John (Box 27)
  - Hertzberg, Sidney (Box 27)
  - Heslop, Harold (Box 27)
  - Hicks, Dorothy, 1924-1945; undated; 2 folders (Box 27)
  - Hicks, Marion, See Doran, Marion.
  - Hicks, Stephanie (Box 27)
  - Hicks' relatives (Box 27)
  - Higgins, George Gilmary (Box 27)
  - Hill and Wang, Inc. (Box 27)
  - Hill School Paideia Conference (Box 27)
  - Hillegas, Mark Robert (Box 27)
  - Hillman, Serrell (Box 27)
  - Hills, L. Rust (Box 27)
  - Hillyer, Robert S. (Box 27)
  - Hilsenrath, Edgar (Box 27)
  - Himes, Norman Edwin (Box 27)
  - Hitch, Earle (Box 27)
  - Hobson, Laura Keane Z. (Box 28)
  - Hoch, Edward D. (Box 28)
  - Hoff, Marilyn (Box 28)
  - Hoffman, Daniel G. (Box 28)
  - Hollander, Herbert S. (Box 28)
  - Hollister, Paul (Box 28)
  - Holmes, Eugene Clay (Box 28)
  - Holmes, John Haynes (Box 28)
  - Holroyd, Donald L. (Box 28)
  - Holt, Alfred Hubbarb (Box 28)
  - Henry Holt and Company (Box 28)
  - Holt, Rinehart and Winston, Inc. (Box 28)
  - Honan, Park (Box 28)
  - Hook, Sidney (Box 28)
  - Hopwood Awards (Box 28)
  - Horgan, Daniel F. (Box 28)
  - Horizon Press, Inc. (Box 28)
  - Hornberger, Theodore (Box 28)
  - Hornbrook, Ruth (Box 28)
  - Hornstein, Lillian Herlands (Box 28)
  - Hosoiri, Totaro (Box 28)
  - Houghton, A.S. (Box 28)
  - Houghton Mifflin Company (Box 28)
  - The Hound and Horn (Box 28)
  - House, Julius Temple (Box 28)
  - The House Committee on Un-American Activities (Box 28)
  - Hovey, Carl (Box 28)
  - Hovey, Richard (Box 28)
  - Howard, Joseph Kinsey (Box 28)
  - Howe, Edgar Watson (Box 28)
  - Howe, Helen Huntington (Box 28)
  - Howe, Irving (Box 28)
  - Howe, Quincy (Box 28)
  - Howells, Mildred (Box 28)
  - Howells, William Dean, 2 folders (Box 28)
  - Howes, Barbara (Box 28)
  - Howes, Elizabeth Boyden (Box 28)
  - Huberman, Leo (Box 28)
  - Hudson, William Henry (Box 28)
  - Hudson Review (Box 28)
  - Hughes, H. Stuart (Box 28)
  - Hughes, Langston (Box 28)
  - Hugo, Howard E. (Box 28)
  - Hull, Andrew P. (Box 28)
  - Humanism (Box 28)
  - Humanities Review (Box 28)
  - Humphries, Rolfe (Box 28)
  - Humphries, Wilfred R. (Box 28)
  - Hunt, Edward Eyre (Box 28)
  - Hunt, Lyman C. (Box 28)
  - Huntington Hartford Foundation (Box 28)
  - Hutchins, Grace (Box 28)
  - Hutchinson, Paul (Box 28)
  - Huxley, Aldous (Box 28)
  - Hyman, Stanley Edgar (Box 28)
  - Hyndman, Henry Mayers (Box 28)
  - I (Box 29)
  - I Like America, 1938-1947; undated; 5 folders (Box 29)
  - Illinois, University of (Box 29)
  - Illinois Writers' Project. Cavalcade of the American Negro, See Common Council for American Unity.
  - Iman, Raymond S. (Box 29)
  - Impact Publications (Box 29)
  - Imperialism (Box 29)
  - Independent Left (Box 29)
  - Indiana (State) (Box 29)
  - Indiana University (Box 29)
  - Indiana University Press (Box 29)
  - Institute for Community Leadership (Box 29)
  - Intellectuals (Box 29)
  - Interim (Box 29)
  - International Labor Defense (Box 29)
  - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (Box 29)
  - International Literature (Box 29)
  - International Publishers (Box 29)
  - International Student Service of the United States (Box 29)
  - Irving, Washington (Box 29)
  - Irwin, William Henry (Box 29)
  - Isherwood, Christopher (Box 29)
  - Iverson, Robert W., See Fund for the Republic.
  - J (Box 29)
  - Jackson, Charles (Box 29)
  - Jackson, Katherine Gauss (Box 29)
  - Jackson, Shirley (Box 29)
  - Jacobs, Judy (Box 29)
  - Jaffa, Herbert C. (Box 29)
  - James, Henry, 2 folders (Box 29)
  - Jameson, Storm (Box 30)
  - Janeway, Elizabeth (Box 30)
  - Janik, Phyllis (Box 30)
  - Jarvis, Ralph D. (Box 30)
  - Jeffers, Una (Call) (Box 30)
  - Jeffrey, Mildred Mesurac (Box 30)
  - Jellema, Roderick (Box 30)
  - Jelliffe, Belinda Dobson (Box 30)
  - Jerard, Elise (Box 30)
  - Jewett, Sarah Orne (Box 30)
  - Johns, Judith Clancy, See Clancy, Judith S..
  - Johns, Orrick (Box 30)
  - Johnson, Allan, See Schachner, Eugene.
  - Johnson, Allen, See Dictionary of American Biography.
  - Johnson, Alvin Saunders, See Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences.
  - Johnson, Josephine (Box 30)
  - Johnson, Oakley (Box 30)
  - Johnson, Pyke (Box 30)
  - Jones, Claude Edward (Box 30)
  - Jones, Ellis O. (Box 30)
  - Jones, H.G. (Box 30)
  - Jones, Howard Mumford (Box 30)
  - Jones, James (Box 30)
  - Jones, John Hudson (Box 30)
  - Jones, Lombard C. (Box 30)
    See also Walton, Edith (Mrs. L.C. Jones).
  - Jones, Madison (Box 30)
  - Jones, Robert Edmond (Box 30)
  - Joseph, Donald (Box 30)